when I found hideous.
The first thing that wanted know about was the spire, not Meridian.
The spire.
Now why would that be?
Spire was created by Goya.
Which part of God
Minerva?
It's codebreaking.
Module Guy built spires to transmit the codes that deactivated the pharaoh Robots shut down their bio matter conversion systems.
Haiti's wants to send a new transmission to wake the machines so they can devour the world all over again.
Yes, based on what we learned.
That's my conclusion as well.
So the eclipse, the robot's they've resurrected.
They're just a means to an end.
An army to capture the spire.
Yes.
So Haiti's can exterminate life all over again.
Look at this
way to relieve you.
You give me.
Don't ask me to go.
Lost
fire.
Rescue.
She was better.
A moment like this.
I've seen better.
I've seen this before.
Cancer lady
manager.
Looking anywhere.
They also have gone too far.
The vaults are dark.
It's always the ones you least expect.
Wait,
You stink.
What
a lawyer.
What brings you to Meridia?
A threat?
Hey, Lis Command.
A legion of fanatics called the eclipse.
They will attack soon from the West with an army of ancient war machines.
But that's not the worst of it.
They'll bring a mind with them.
God, demon machine, whatever you want to call it.
It's called Haiti's
and it doesn't want Meridian at all.
It wants the spire.
And if it gets there, it will send out a call waking more ancient machines more than we could ever defeat.
All will be lost.
We can't let that happen.
I'm trying to understand.
But my responsibility lies with Meridia.
Meridian isn't the target of odd.
You have to defend the spire.
Perhaps the vanguard.
Your radiance.
Yes.
Send them to the spire.
Aaron knows a lawyer.
He won't question it.
And have the city guard fortify the Western ridge.
There they could be seen to protect Meridian on the alight with Speyer rests.
A lawyer.
Allow me to.
I apologise for my behaviour.
Before,
After everything that happened with our son,
I was confused.
If we're to fight together on the brink of life and death, I'd prefer to do so with your forgiveness.
Then you have it as long as you don't confuse me with her again.
Even a king can learn his lesson.
Good.
Then I'm glad that's behind us.
No.
It will take time to prepare our defences.
Please tell me what you know of our enemies.
Everything.
I don't know about everything.
But I'll tell you what I can.
Have you spoken to blameless Murad?
Not yet.
But I will say wishes to speak to defensive preparations.
Are his responsibility
quietly, Does it?
Panic in the city will only create another enemy.
And do keep me appraised of each new arrival.
Oh boy.
Preparations are underway on the ridge of defences and that Aspire word was sent to every corner of the Sunda MME.
Our allies offered their steel.
Some came from a ready and others for shards.
But many came for you.
My name
for me.
Don't be so humble, I suppose all we can do is wait for the attack.
Exactly.
It's not a feeling I cherish, but our spotter that evening sign report.
There's still no movement in the West.
The ridge will be the front line.
That's where the city guard are holding.
Yes, bolstered by some of the irregulars the Oscar arm cannons that thundered meridians wolves in the liberation.
Well, now defend us.
You're welcome to tour the defences on the spire errand in the vanguard of there, indeed, clashing breastplates together and testing out their battle cries.
I suppose a number of the Nora have also arrived at Aspire.
They have resisted the offer of a royal audience.
Perhaps you could parley with them.
I will.
So if there's more you need to do elsewhere sees this time to do it.
Otherwise, I've made the apartment of Olden Dellaverson available to you.
You can sleep there if sleep comes.
I've reached the main case.
Gather bows and spears.
Don't let them take the city without a fight.
I'm fine.
Your brother
Could you spare a moment to speak of the finer things?
These are jerks.
Watch pied.
Here's to a
address
by this sun Woman now leads the Hunter's lodge.
What's next?
A woman is king.
Have you just polished that armour?
Who's it?
Of course.
Isn't that a little?
What?
Nothing.
Out with a woman.
You forget I said anything.
You look very dignified.
Thank you.
And shiny.
Very shiny.
Hey, Louie,
I told you I'd be here.
You did tub, but have your wounds even had time to heal.
Honestly, if I fought, I probably.
Come on gun.
But don't worry.
I'll leave that to the other north of the spire.
I brought supplies instead.
These cards have made me an honorary quartermaster.
Whatever that means.
It sounds impressive.
I could get used to it.
We'll be setting up caches of arms and medicine under these banners.
Look for them when the fighting starts.
A lawyer
When you went into the mountain,
the goddess I tell you our chances she didn't need Teo.
I know we can do this step.
Maybe you can.
This place, you'll ever placing you couldn't.
Even with different to the sacred land.
There are materials like I've never seen in the markets above.
I tried to explain stitchers and makers to these cards, and you'd think that wouldn't take much explain.
Little Huntress, you called.
So here I am.
Ready to fight?
Fight?
I thought you just wanted tea and conversation.
Is there a battle coming?
I wasn't informed.
Well, that can't be true.
You're always informed.
No.
So I am.
We've only met a few times.
And yet you know me so well.
I don't think I know you at all,
but I'd like to
when I hear that line.
It usually means something else.
Can I tell you a secret?
Of course.
I've been waiting for this fight my whole life.
The enemy we face today is the same that turned Meridian in tow.
A slave pit and sun fall into a blood bath.
Fanatics who torture and murder mothers, fathers, families, Children and say it's the will of the sun.
I hate them.
A Loy.
I've got the scars of the whips of my back to prove it.
And today we can get rid of them once and for all.
I said I came for you, but that was only half the truth.
I came for them this time.
They're not getting away.
I'm with you, Verne.
ASHA.
We'll fight them together and I won't forget it.
Little huntress
tomorrow made the sun rise in a better world.
I only fight when I have to, but by the time I have to, I usually want to.
I put something special on the tips of my arrows for the eclipse.
It's too bad, but have us isn't here to see his little friends crushed.
Hey, Lloyd.
Um, at ease with it.
Meridian will be glad to have you on its side and I am too.
The honour is mine.
You saved my epitaph from being a fine soldier but a fool of a man.
I'm hoping you won't need any kind of epitaphs just yet.
As the sun wills
When you found me, I was trying to eke out of Gloria's death.
But now a glorious life seems more preferable to watch Letterman playing the low gardens again, still surrounded by a dozen guards.
But
what you did a lawyer,
It was done well.
Although I can't shake this road, The nausea she delights in goading me like brazen colours wave before a behemoth.
Do you want me to ask her to stop?
No,
I accept it Well In
birdie in, she'll stand and shadow shall fall.
I swear it.
Here's to that.
If it
the sun is my armour His other armoury where it's a safeguard
always for a son King always for Meridian
every battle we hope to make the last for the other side.
How many men do you think you're doing?
Battle
as many as I have to.
I love it when you say things like that.
It's so what cheerful
Elita, I'm pleased to see you, but what are you doing here?
I'm helping.
Prepare for the battle.
If a troll were here, we would have fought together.
I know it.
So I'm doing everything I can.
Digging battlements, collecting herbs, anything that makes a difference.
I can't take his place.
Nothing can take this place.
But I'm here for him.
For both of us.
I understand what it was he saw in you.
He'll always be with me.
Sun and shadow still meet for a moment.
Every dawn and dusk.
I should give you this to help in the battle
by the sun.
I hope you don't need it.
Thank you, Alina.
Be safe.
Father understood that I couldn't just stand by in my garden.
Maybe this battle can finally end the war between the car.
Jack.
I should finish up here before the fighting starts.
That's a nice speer.
Thank you.
I like the way you grip it.
Enough.
Nicole, You came to fight?
How could I not?
During the red raids, there was only one card to butcher.
The Nora feared more than Zaid.
He was I would stand against any army he leads, no matter how strong For the nor he terrorised for myself and for my father.
We'll stop him.
You have my word.
Your word means a lot.
Especially now Because of you.
I hear the sacred land is open.
If we win, I can go home.
It'll be good to see you on again.
I'm with you, a lawyer
until the end.
Like you said, we'll stop.
Hell is cold together.
I hear they call you the Anointed.
Now the Matrix and the rituals.
John's probably eating it up.
It's strange to fight alongside the Kharja, but I guess they're like any tribe.
Some kind.
Some vicious
Geneva.
They called you back to duty.
So you're the one behind all this commotion Who made Sun King of odd finally showed his sword on from behind those robes.
A king can be fierce and fair.
Geneva He's a good man.
A smart man too.
He had Murad offer all my prisoners a royal pardon.
If they'd fight for Meridian.
The whole motley lot of them agreed.
Didn't take much convincing with your kind of convincing.
I don't doubt it hot this time I went easy on them.
Those who commit the crime of attacking Meridian, they'll see less of my leaning side.
May the sun blazes You're back.
A Loy
can't fault my prisoners.
Discipline!
All those dawn drills have served him well after it's all over.
That might be the only one going back to the rock.
How'd you like that?
I've waited two years for this water break.
I can wait a little longer.
Isn't that him?
From the battle of the dog, I can't.
Cinnabar Sands was before never no survivors.
Well, I don't like to boast Some keep the shadow from falling upon me.
Killed anyone lately you'd like to talk about?
No.
Hey,
they told me your name.
I said hair like a splash of blood.
Tenacious is scrappers jobs?
I've thought about what you said
every time the wounds you gave me caught in my ribs.
But I didn't wound you.
No, not yet.
Still, I forgive a duel is such a fleeting joy.
If one of us that ended the other, we have missed all this.
Wait for the ship.
Like the scrape of a blade across your teeth.
You're making it difficult to be glad to see you,
but you're needed.
The battle will be hard, Hard.
I was assured the odds would be near impossible.
And you signed up anyway.
Impossible odds find company killing without consequence.
How could I resist?
I don't care for fighting machines, but I hear these ones of demons.
That's exciting.
Trouble with a battle is it could be hard to find Killer to call you
Petro.
Here she is the guest of honour.
I knew there was something about you hammered from the stuff they make leaders out of.
And I don't say that to every nor a girl who blows through my town.
That happens to you a lot.
I had to build a wall to fend them off.
Good thing I'm persistent than
I've missed our little talks.
Murad asked me to look over the city Arsenal.
These guns of aged Well, that runs in the Ostrom.
No, They were the pride of the Mainspring forges.
So I've taken greater pride in improving them.
Can I try one?
Everybody wants a turn.
Have at it then.
The target should put up a little less of a fight than those bandit Raiders did.
Range is good.
Try the next
with these.
I'm not a machine on staff.
Ancient or no
No need to pay me like a bow,
you know that.
I appreciate your help, Petra,
This battle
I don't know what's gonna happen.
We'll see each other again.
I know it.
Next time could be the time.
I'll convince you to stick with the free heap.
You know, I D'oh!
I do always had a weakness for restless girls.
Though
I don't make weapons for a living, it's more of a diversion.
The city always ground my gears.
But I'd miss it if it were gone.
You take care of yourself and the cannons.
Our talk.
I didn't expect you to come all this way.
It is true.
I am a stranger in this green and snow, This land
array.
I forgave the cars.
Yeah, but I never did.
Still, I was compelled to come from my ones.
Chieftain!
It's good to see you leading again.
This one of nowhere, AC.
He may have taken too many blows to the head, but he's a good fighter and strong.
This young eyes hunter seeks to prove herself.
Also her spark reminds me of a raise and our youth.
And I'm proud to take my place behind you on this hunt.
a great challenge.
Survive and prevail, right?
There is no other way.
Did we not fight back machine demons before you?
My sister and I?
The battle looms.
But every day brings a fresh battle.
Zion said she could not predict the outcome.
If she had,
I would have chosen not to hear it.
Have you come to defend my honour?
Hit it.
I know you don't need any help with that, but from all I've heard, you've found yourself a good fight here.
So I'll stand this ground with you.
You won't have ever seen a fight like this.
And we only get one shot at it.
I've been told I'm in over my head before, nor a girl.
You know what I say?
I'm always in over my head.
That I centre doesn't talk much except to herself.
I'm ready.
You wanna punch my guts?
He already I am.
No.
I choose my own battles now and I choose this one.
You are the hunter from the new Growth.
I remember.
You also, Nora.
The machine shook free of their slumber after you arrived, raged and fought.
Uh, well, that that wasn't my fault.
No, I'm thanking you that night I decided I would not go back to banner.
I would take my hunt into these lands.
So many machines, even demons spied Aries skittering without the blue light in them dead things that must be killed again.
Our enemy's dug up an army of them.
An army?
Yes.
That's why I came.
Good.
I'll wait from their metal bones.
I'll make my armour and my song.
My spear is sharp.
My will is like the oldest ice.
If I live or die, they'll call my name down Glacier cracks.
Alana, why are you here?
And your hawk?
Where else would I be defending Meridian with Abad.
I leave that to the rest of the lodge.
I will not stand aside while one of mine fights alone.
Not again.
Are you sure you're risking your life for all of us?
You can't ask me to stand by and watch.
Not when I have the power to change it.
Then I won't ask you.
It's settled.
I will fight by your side.
My only request.
Name it.
Leave the biggest machine for me.
No promises.
When you need me, I'll follow your lead.
I came prepared.
Have arrows!
Enough to take down five armies hawk and thrush ready for the battle to start.
It rises taller than the highest tree.
These cards are in their frilled armour Look like turkeys.
But there are so many.
And now we are so few.
They're not our fault.
Not this time.
Quiet!
Now come the anointed
war Chief Sona,
War Chief, you You seem uncomfortable.
The Nora do not belong here.
I do not belong here.
I will fight the metal devil that threatens us all.
But my place is in the secret land.
Wrongness here jags of me like an arrow head.
I'm sorry to put you through this.
Do not be sorry.
This will be ended.
My spear, My word.
The card you do not impress me to build so tall is to invite the fate of the ancients.
We will stand tall for we are the strength of the Nora.
Your fight is ours.
You know it to be so.
Oh great son, How does your gaze fall?
An approval
or approach?
Turn our heads with your daily pilgrimage from the east where we came to the west where only you may go.
You grant cold metal the warmth of life and let the machines bask in your great shining for you the shadow shrink and part and gather again on Lee at your allowance without form your eyes, the day, your ears, the priests, your lips, the radiant sun King as there was before and will be again
your life.
No, man.
I should have known if there was gonna be a son priest here it would be you.
And if the Sun King had allowed outlanders to set foot upon the alight, it's a lawyer could only be you.
I was the circumstance to a different although the Psalms of the Sun could give you peace of mind.
But if you allow me one pontification, go ahead.
You've shown strength and compassion, our enemies only a desperate hate.
Both sides claimed the blessing of the sun, but the son that I pray to it would bestow it upon yours.
You know, Norman, I'm already under some pretty heavy divine pressure, but I'll try to live up to it.
The tribes united against shadow.
How could that not be?
The sons will,
From what I could gather the nor believe their God has chosen for a fated battle
it isn't.
Greetings.
A Loy
don't.
You don't need to bow.
The anointed doesn't like it.
She doesn't much like being called anointed either.
It means a lot to have you here, Varro.
I gave my word.
So, Meridian, what do you think?
I've seen many new things since I first met you.
I should thank you for all.
What's wrong?
You really want to know?
All right.
I'm in a foreign land, a tainted land defending a faithless city.
That looks like nothing I've seen from something I can't imagine.
And you, After all that's happened, all you've done, I feel like I should drop to my knees and worship you.
But I know you don't want that boy.
Things are pretty tough for you, huh?
Thanks for telling the other Nora not to bow.
It's the last thing I need.
Yeah,
don't be too hard on them.
They only joined this fight because the united bit itself.
Is that why you came?
No.
I would have come just to see you one more time.
And we must fight a metal devil because the goddess says or because you say I think the goddess and I are in agreement.
We're both glad you're here.
So am I.
You're friend.
Vanguard keeps looking over
up here.
I'm not sure if the world's growing bigger.
Where I've grown smaller.
I apologise for the war, Chief.
She is hating this.
Who are these guys?
They call themselves the Eclipse.
What does that even mean?
It's when the moon gets in front of the sun.
Idiot.
Is that supposed to sound scary or something?
I don't know.
Used to be cards.
Cards are always yammering about sun and shade.
Well, if they used to be Kharja, how tough can they be?
Yeah, their best guys, just like birds will rip their little feathers off.
Let's not get cocky, boys.
Hey, Lloyd.
So here we are again, gearing up for a fight.
Well, this time it sounds like the bad guys have a lot more firepower.
What are we up against?
Really?
I'm not sure, but there's gonna be a lot of them and they'll have machines.
And if they get past us, it's not just Meridian that will fall.
The rest of the world will go with it.
That's
big.
It sounds like our kind of fight.
Right, guys, where do they put the vanguard at the front of the line.
And why seal for iron?
What are we gonna do?
Hit him like a cannon back.
Damn right.
You hear that?
Nobody's getting past the vanguard.
We're here from Meridian,
and we're here for you.
Thank you, Aaron.
Her son would be proud.
Only if we win.
We're gonna fight soon.
I'm getting hungry.
You're always hungry.
Feasts on me after we win.
Beer, too.
You just can't leave me alone, can you?
I think she likes you.
You're gonna kiss her, Captain.
Shut up!
Now we'll just pretend that never happened.
Work day, citizen.
Don't ask me to go if you're lost my guard, Not the town crier.
Not ready and fall without a fight.
Rally car!
Jack,
You're not.
Send them
cover with soldiers.
Do their jobs.
Cheque out this way.
Right!
Get to safety.
Battle begins.
It's nothing
who leads the attack is that he was him.
And the card and Shadow
bones apartment
feels
empty.
Should I sleep?
Did I leave anything unfinished?
How could you sleep Elizabeth with wait like this?
Pressing on you?
How did you rust
after you lost your family?
Silence
are you there.
I guess I shouldn't ask.
Goes for advice.
The Chronicle of the Sun King's founder Arman, who guided our forefathers from the shadows of the Savage East into the vastness of the Mesa Valley and who, reading the signs of sun and shadow both delivered them to the site of Holy Meridian.
Bounteous um Murad, who oversaw the clearing and sowing of the royal Maze land so that none who walked in the sun's favour should go hungry again.
Who cut back the jewel to claim the richest state lands for the first houses of the Sun Court.
The far seeing Sahin who expanded the sun's Dominion to the north, south and east, setting a gated bright market harbour and who, before the sun at its highest, proclaimed these lands would be known as the car just Sunday, Um, so by the light.
It was good, generous Jordan, who stopped the metal markets with the spoils of his own traveller hunts and who allowed trade from north and south, even permitting outlanders.
The gift of the counting cliffs so they might understand more than simple border is ever read.
Pilgrim son King, who's tower, was raised to the top of the ridge of Bales and who crossed the great waters of the daybreak so the Sunda might extend ever further.
And to honour this passage had the great blaze and arch raised on the far shores
who saw the son's passing into the West is a challenge and forged after it with a great army to be pushed back three times in the Great Canyon lands that would be known as the dawn until, on the fourth time his code word broke through and we're vanished in the lands beyond prudent, positive, who had the mantle of his fallen brothers thrust upon him.
Suddenly, we ordered the construction of the fortress of Sun File in the garrison in blazing arch, declaring the land beyond the forbidden West, where only the Sun Meiko who fought in the returner who strove to bring civilisation to the savage East but returned after many strenuous endeavours, saying it was no longer fit for the people of the sun and called for the building of great towers and walls.
So this wild land might be observed safely Renowned Firebird who saw the sun them suffer unprovoked attack by the tender support and who against the protests of his advisors, accompanied his army to confront them under the sun.
He claimed victory though he was so greatly scarred he War is blazing helmet from that day basis who was a hunter as much as a Sun King and called for the proudest men of the noble houses to prove themselves in competition beneath the sun, and that those who felt the greatest machines would be situated.
As the first Sun Hawk and hawks of the Hunters launch, Thie illuminated Mars it who this unvisited with vision so vivid and grant.
He commissioned many statues and frescoes of his visage in Meridian and for his summer palace in Sun File, had the Great Citadel raised where he remained painting until he took deathly ill from his own pigments.
Elder brother of Mars it who decreed each family with a suitable male child should submit that child in service of the Sunda Me's been depleted ranks.
And had the artisans turned their attention from works of art, do outfitting each soldier of the sun with the very finest armour Jalbert in both.
Darren, who in his early years was a strong son, King defending the Sunday from the encroachment of other tribes and the derangement of the machines, but who became greatly Adam and ordered the spilling of much blood in the son's name, threatening to bring a twilight time upon us of ithe Liberator.
Last time I visited Prime was November of last year.
Months since have been a blur flew out last night to oversee installation of the central armature in the Master Override.
You're welcome, Ted, which was completed by all 4 30.
So I decided to grab a few hours of sleep here before heading back to D called before I bet it down, ostensibly to update her on the site plan.
But the truth is, I missed her.
I've developed a habit of speaking to her before I sleep.
Seems to be the only thing that calms me these days.
Woke to a message for Ma's fault, The Odyssey launched yesterday.
Some terrestrial life chance of survival has doubled.
Why, then, do I feel so uneasy?
I just keep wondering what kind of world far Zenith were created.
The ship reaches its destination so many decades from now, and I worry about that Alfa build of Apollo so much knowledge, so few restraints and no fail safe.
So how will they avoid repeating our mistakes?
What's to stop them from playing God forwarded the honesty message to the Alphas?
No, Oto replied in less than a minute with a poem, of course.
The building of the ship by Longfellow and its long all right.
I didn't read all of it, but it seems to be about launching a ship rather than building one stanza were coupling or whatever left out at me.
Humanity, with all its fears with all its hopes of future years, is hanging breathless.
Sound life eight.
Yeah, Odyssey and zero Don both.
Speaking of which I should get back to set, I guess I should stop by no photos.
Lab and cheque on the meter's progress, too.
If I could get out of there without a volume of tennis and pressed into my hands, I'll count myself lucky till next time.
This place you'll ever places you couldn't be more different to the sacred land
Halloween.
Travis came by trick or treating.
Dressed up like me should have seen that coming.
I gave him a half eaten package of dandy wafers as a treat and kicked him out, but not before he invited me to some kind of Italian horror extravaganza he organised for sandy staff, seriously, as though there isn't enough horror in the world already, anyway, I was already scheduled to fly out here to G Prime for final inspections with Harrison, the president's delegation.
Ted was here, too, and he was not looking good, kept fidgeting and couldn't seem to look me in the face without blinking.
I was relieved when he boarded his bird and flew back to Thebes.
Gag, though I guess I shouldn't complain if he wants to build himself a deluxe shelter to ride out the apocalypse, Let him keeps him out of Elysium and away from me.
Harris stuck around long enough to give me a detailed briefing on the strategic situation.
Basically, we've entered the terminal phase as though the colour of the sky when I was flying over here wasn't clue enough.
Another two or three weeks and the atmosphere won't be breathable.
Last vestiges of European and West African souk brigades air trapped with their backs against the Atlantic.
The swarm that scuttled across Antarctica is crossing the Straits of Magellan, about to start its death crawl up South America towards the Amazon.
All the work we did to reconstitute the rain forest and it comes to this and advanced elements of the Pacific swarms are already skirmishing with units on the Kalmar seawall.
Noose is tightening.
Projections show we can still finish in time, but the margin of error is plus or minus 10 days.
Not a good spread if the plague breaks through ahead of schedule.
Well, it just can't.
I will not let that happen.
Enough writing.
I need to get back to zero Don
Such a close thing.
It's been want 43 hours since Harris warned me, said collapse of the eastern line was imminent.
Swarms launching some kind of pincer manoeuvre versus the Wichita salient five or six days more and I think I could have launched without our help.
I really do.
Way had to scramble his F d became a madhouse.
Absolute bedlam.
Every team rushing to stabilise code and lock it down as Gammas got evacuated.
Then babies.
Once Kaya was on her way, I gathered the office together to give them the bad news.
I felt like I was going to throw up, but they already knew.
Of course, they knew the work wasn't really finished.
Close, but not quite there.
Still tests to run.
Kings, too smooth work to do so they accepted it.
Noel Easy impress.
We'll spend the rest of our lives here testing and polishing each subordinate function to perfection.
Guess that's what you get when you recruit a bunch of obsessive perfectionists managed not to cry until I got back to my office.
So here we are, setting up a guy a prime.
And, yeah, such a close thing makes me feel nauseated all over again when I contemplate how the fate of life could hinge on coincidence.
If I'd never proposed the light keeper protocol, there never would have been living space is constructed here.
If I had abandoned the protocol sooner necessary, life support systems never would have been installed if if if at least we won't have to endure the creepiness of racing and training clones of ourselves.
The genetic material was never processed out of the cradle sites.
So it's not even possible for which I'm glad I really, really wouldn't want to spend time around a young Travis State raised by Travis State.
No, it will be up to us to perfect one generation on ly update.
That was General Harris.
The salient has collapsed.
U S R.
C expects to be overrun in two days, which gives us 72 hours at best to lock down and seal up buried alive for life State.
I'll go tell the others.